Guide to the Horace Dwight Taft Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Horace Dwight Taft papers
1888-1983
MS 1399
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
34.5
(85 boxes)
The papers consist of correspondence, topical files, and physics files which document Taft's career as a professor and researcher in physics and as an administrator at Yale University. While the majority of records created during Taft's tenure as master of Davenport College and dean of Yale College are within the University Archives, Taft maintained some correspondence from these offices within his personal papers. His personal files contain correspondence with his parents and other family members, diaries, and student notebooks and papers. As a member of the board of the Taft School, Taft maintained files of correspondence, board meeting minutes, reports, and printed material from 1953-1983.
Taft, Horace Dwight, 1925-1983
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Mrs. Horace D. Taft, 1985.
Arrangement
Arranged in three series: I. Correspondence and Topical Files, 1888-1983. II. Teaching Files, 1941-1982. III. Physics Files, 1947-1983.
Scope and Contents
The Horace Dwight Taft Papers consist of correspondence, topical files, teaching files, and physics files which document Taft's career as a professor and researcher in physics and as an administrator at Yale University. The papers were the gift of Mrs. Horace Dwight Taft in 1985. The 34.5 linear feet of papers are arranged in three series: I.CORRESPONDENCE AND TOPICAL FILES, II.TEACHING FILES, and III.PHYSICS FILES.
Series I, CORRESPONDENCE AND TOPICAL FILES, consists of alphabetically arranged files containing material which documents Taft's professional and personal activities. Correspondence, grant proposals, annual reports and budgets document physics projects which Taft conducted during his tenure at. Yale in conjunction with the Atomic Energy Commission, the Department of Energy, and the Argonne, Brookhaven, Fermi, and National Accelerator laboratories. Additional material relating to these projects may be found in Series III. Taft's service on advisory panels and committees of numerous professional organizations, and his participation in national and international conferences are documented by correspondence and subject files including those of the American Physical Society, the High Energy Physics Advisory Panel, and the International Conference on High Energy Physics.
While the majority of records created during Taft's tenure as master of Davenport College and dean of Yale College are within the University Archives, Taft maintained some correspondence from these offices within his personal Yale files. Taft's administrative and committee activities at Yale, including the Committee on Academic Computing, the Committee on Energy Conservation, the Course of Study Committee, and the Tobin Committee, are documented by correspondence and printed material.
Personal files within the series include correspondence with family members and friends, diaries dating from 1964 to 1983, student notebooks and typescripts of his doctoral thesis chapters, and various personal memorabilia. Writings files containing preprints and reprints of Taft's articles dating from 1956 to 1982, and speeches given at Yale, the Taft School, and other institutions, are also included in the series. As a member of the board of trustees of the Taft School, Taft maintained files of correspondence, board meeting minutes, reports, and printed material dating from 1953 to 1983.
Following the alphabetically arranged correspondence and topical files in this series, is a chronological run of correspondence pertaining to personal and professional subjects.
Series II, TEACHING FILES, consists of course files containing syllabi, lecture notes, problems, examinations, and class lists. Additional files within the series contain graduate student and physics majors data, thesis proposals, and physics department curriculum and departmental examination information.
Series III, PHYSICS FILES, contains notes, data, computer tapes and print-outs, and miscellaneous material relating to physics projects which Taft conducted. As the files are arranged as they were received from Taft's office, there is some overlap between material in this and other series.
Biographical / Historical
Horace Dwight Taft was born in Cincinnati, Ohio on April 2, 1925, the son of Senator Robert A. and Martha Bowers Taft, and grandson of President William Howard Taft. He attended the Taft School in Watertown, Connecticut, which was founded by a grand-uncle, Horace Dutton Taft. After serving in the United States Army from 1943 to 1946, Taft enrolled in Yale University and received a Bachelor of Arts degree in 1950. Taft was a research assistant and studied under Enrico Fermi at the University of Chicago, where he received a master's degree (1953) and a Ph.D. (1955) in physics.
Taft joined the Yale faculty in 1956 as an instructor in physics, and was appointed a professor in 1964. He was master of Davenport College from 1966 to 1971, and dean of Yale College from 1971 to 1979. He served on numerous university committees and was director of undergraduate studies in physics.
Taft's research in 1962 with a group of American and European physicists led to the discovery and identification of one of the last predicted antimatter particles, known as the anti-XI-minus. The discovery helped establish the symmetry between matter and antimatter, a form of matter in which the property of each particle is the reverse of the usual matter in the universe. With Professor Irwin Pless of the Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Taft developed a device to help physicists read automatically the photographs of paths of subatomic particles and to extract highly specific kinds of information from them. At the time of his death he was involved in research to find a particle called the Tau-neutrino.
Taft was married to Mary Jane Badger. They had three sons, John G. Taft, Hugh B. Taft-Morales, and Horace D. Taft. Horace Dwight Taft died in New Haven, Connecticut on February 11, 1983.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Particles (Nuclear physics); Physicists; Taft, Horace Dwight, 1925-1983; Taft, Robert, Jr., 1917-1993; Taft School; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University -- Officals and employees; Yale University. Physics Department
- Correspondence and Topical Files, 1888-1983; Series I; 18.5' (45 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains correspondence and topical files arranged alphabetically by personal, corporate, or subject name, followed by a run of correspondence arranged chronologically by year.
  - American Physical Society
    - Division of Particles and Fields, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - General, 1962-1975 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
    - General, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Panel on Public Affairs
      - Arms control, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Breeder reaction study, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Education, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Export controls, 1980-1981, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Funding of research, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Meetings: agenda and minutes, 1980 January-Dec, 1981 January-Apr, 1982, undated (Box 1, Folder 10-13)
      - Meetings: minutes and miscellaneous material, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous reports, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous reports, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Public affairs, 1980-1982, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Studies, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Study on alternative energy approaches, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Study on alternative energy approaches, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Study on research planning for coal utilization and synthetic fuel production, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Subcommittee on International Scientific Affairs, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Subcommittee on National Scientific Affairs, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Women's issues, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Workshop, 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 25-26)
  - Argonne National Laboratory, 1962-1966, 1971, undated (Box 2, Folder 27-28)
  - Atomic Energy Commission
    - Annual Inventory Report on Automatic Data Processing, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Annual Inventory Report on Automatic Data Processing, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Annual Inventory Report on Automatic Data Processing, 1968-1973, undated (Box 3, Folder 31-33)
    - Computer report, 1963-1966 January-August (Box 3, Folder 34-35)
    - Computer report, 1966 October-December (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Computer report, 1967, undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Computing funds, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence, 1961-1973 (Box 3, Folder 39-41)
    - General services, administration, and surplus, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Miscellaneous notes, 1968-1974, undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Program budgets
      - FY-1962-1965, 1961-1964 (Box 3, Folder 44)
      - FY 1966, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 45)
      - FY 1967, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - FY 1968, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - FY 1968, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - FY 1970, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 49)
      - FY 1971, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - FY 1972-1974, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - FY 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - FY 1974, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - FY 1973-1976, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - FY 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Semi-annual Report on Accomplishments in Automatic Data Processing, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Semi-annual Report on Accomplishments in Automatic Data Processing, 1971-1973, undated (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory, 1977-1982 (Box 5, Folder 58-59)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory. High Energy Discussion Group, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Disadvantaged businesses, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Energy, 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Fermi National Accelerator Laboratory, 1964-1971 (Box 5, Folder 63-69)
  - Fermi National Accelerator Laboratory, 1972-1978 (Box 6, Folder 70-78)
  - Fermi National Accelerator Laboratory, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 79-82)
  - Fermi National Accelerator Laboratory: Bubble Chamber Survey, 1970-1973, undated (Box 7, Folder 83-88)
  - Fermi National Accelerator Laboratory: Neutrino Area Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Fermi National Accelerator Laboratory: Neutrino Area Committee, undated (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Fermi National Accelerator Laboratory: Tevatron Program Workshop, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Fermi National Accelerator Laboratory: Trilling Committee, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Gibbs Society, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Heavy quark spectrometer meeting notes, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    General
    See also: box 24, folders 294-297
  - High Energy Physics Advisory Panel (HEPAP)
    - Bubble chamber contribution, 1968, undated (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - Miscellaneous material, 1968 January-April (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - Miscellaneous material, 1968 May-1970, undated (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - Princeton-Pennsylvania Accelerator Presentation, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - Subcommittee on Computer Usage
      - Argonne National Laboratory, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 99-100)
      - Brenner, A. E., 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 101)
      - Brown, Richard, 1969, undated (Box 8, Folder 102)
      - Central computing facilities, 1969-1970, undated (Box 8, Folder 103)
      - Computer Usage Survey Summaries, undated (Box 8, Folder 104-105)
      - Consultants, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 106)
      - Correspondence, 1969-1970, undated (Box 9, Folder 107)
      - Curtis, Kent, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 108)
      - Day, Thomas B., 1969 (Box 9, Folder 109)
      - Fields, Thomas, 1969, undated (Box 9, Folder 110)
      - Hildebrand, Bernard, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 111)
      - Hulsizer, Robert, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 112)
      - Kerth, Leroy T., 1969 (Box 9, Folder 113)
      - Leipaner, Lawrence B., 1969 (Box 9, Folder 114)
      - Leith, David W., 1969 (Box 9, Folder 115)
      - Meeting minutes, 1969, undated (Box 9, Folder 116)
      - Miscellaneous material, 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 117)
      - Miscellaneous material, 1970, undated (Box 9, Folder 118-121)
      - Old HEPAP material, 1968, undated (Box 9, Folder 122)
      - On-line facilities, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 123)
      - Remote usage, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 124)
        See also: box 2, folders 27-28
      - Report, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 125)
      - Report, [1970?] (Box 10, Folder 126-127)
      - Report draft, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 128-129)
      - Report draft, [1970?] (Box 10, Folder 130)
      - Report draft, 1970, undated (Box 10, Folder 131)
      - Report draft, undated (Box 10, Folder 132-134)
      - Smith, Charles V. L., 1969 (Box 10, Folder 135)
      - Special topics, 1969, undated (Box 10, Folder 136)
      - Surveys, undated (Box 10, Folder 137)
      - Surveys, undated (Box 11, Folder 138-139)
      - Weiskopf, Victor, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 140)
      - Worksheets, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 141)
    - Sub-panel B, 1966-1967 August-Dec, 1968 January (Box 11, Folder 142-144)
    - Sub-panel B, 1968 March-June (Box 11, Folder 145)
    - Sub-panel B, 1968 July-Dec, undated (Box 11, Folder 146-148)
    - Sub-panel B: Brookhaven National Laboratory meeting, 1967-1968, undated (Box 11, Folder 149)
    - Sub-panel B: Brookhaven National Laboratory meeting report, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 150)
    - Sub-panel B: meeting agenda 1968 Apr 24 (Box 11, Folder 151)
    - Sub-panel B: meeting minutes 1968 Apr 24 (Box 11, Folder 152)
    - Sub-panel B: report, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 153)
    - Sub-panel B: survey of spark chamber film analysis, 1968 February-June (Box 11, Folder 154)
    - Sub-panel B: survey of spark chamber film analysis, 1968 June (Box 12, Folder 155)
    - Sub-panel B: survey of spark chamber film analysis, 1968 July-1969, undated (Box 12, Folder 156)
  - International Hybrid Spectrometer Consortium, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 157)
    - Preprints and reprints, 1974-1979 (Box 12, Folder 158-161)
    - Preprints and reprints, 1981-1982, undated (Box 12, Folder 162-163)
    - Proposals, 1975-1979, undated (Box 12, Folder 164-165)
    - Versus Fermi National Accelerator Laboratory, 1977-1979, undated (Box 12, Folder 166-167)
  - Lobbying, [1980?] (Box 12, Folder 168)
  - Lucas, Peter, 1971-1973, 1979-1982 (Box 13, Folder 169)
  - Ludlam, Thomas, 1970-1978, undated (Box 13, Folder 170)
  - National Accelerator Laboratory (Box 13, Folder 170)
    See also: box 5, folder 63-69
  - National Science Foundation
    - Computer proposal, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 171)
    - First year research proposal, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 172-173)
    - Miscellaneous material, undated (Box 13, Folder 174)
    - Program, 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 175)
    - Second undergraduate research proposal, 1962-1966 (Box 13, Folder 176-177)
    - Summer Institute, undated (Box 13, Folder 178)
    - Third year research proposal, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 179)
    - Undergraduate science education program, 1963-1965, undated (Box 13, Folder 180-181)
  - New York University
    - AEC Computing and Applied Mathematics Center, 1959-1968 (Box 13, Folder 182-184)
    - AEC Computing and Applied Mathematics Center, 1969-1976 (Box 14, Folder 185-187)
  - Nobel Prize, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 188)
  - Personal files
    - Certificates, licenses, and passports, 1950-1952, 1962-1967, 1978, undated (Box 14, Folder 189)
    - Correspondence between H. D. Taft and mother, 1938-1942 (Box 14, Folder 190)
    - Correspondence between H. D. Taft and parents, 1943-1945, undated (Box 14, Folder 191-193)
    - Correspondence between H. D. Taft and wife, 1958, undated (Box 14, Folder 194)
    - Correspondence between Horace D. Taft (great uncle) and Mrs. Robert A. Taft (mother), 1930-1939 (Box 14, Folder 195)
    - Correspondence
      - B (Box 14, Folder 196)
      - C (Box 14, Folder 197)
      - D (Box 14, Folder 198)
      - F (Box 14, Folder 199)
      - G (Box 14, Folder 200)
      - H-J (Box 14, Folder 201)
      - K-L (Box 14, Folder 202)
      - M (Box 14, Folder 203)
      - N-P (Box 15, Folder 204)
      - R (Box 15, Folder 205)
      - S (Box 15, Folder 206)
      - T-Z, unidentified (Box 15, Folder 207)
    - Curriculum vitae, undated (Box 15, Folder 208)
    - Diaries, 1964-1983 (Box 15, Folder 209-211)
    - Diplomas and certificates, 1953-1955, 1971, 1979-1982 (Box 15, Folder 212)
    - Greeting cards, undated (Box 15, Folder 213)
    - Miscellaneous Taft family correspondence, 1888, 1889, 1913 (Box 15, Folder 214)
    - Student notebooks
      - Complete running log (YAP), 1959 December-1960 June (Box 16, Folder 215)
      - Notes for Physics 201, 1952 October-December (Box 16, Folder 216)
      - Notes for Physics 202: differential equations, 1952 January-March (Box 16, Folder 217)
      - Notes for Physics 202, 1952 April-June (Box 16, Folder 218)
      - Notes for Physics 212: mechanics II, 1952 January-March (Box 16, Folder 219)
      - Notes for Physics 221: electricity I, 1952 March-May (Box 16, Folder 220)
      - Notes for Physics 231: experimental physics I, 1952 March-May (Box 16, Folder 221)
      - Notes for Physics 323: electrodynamics and optics II, 1952 January-March (Box 16, Folder 222)
      - Notes for Physics 341-2 [?]: quantum mechanics, 1952 October-December (Box 16, Folder 223)
      - Notes for Physics 341-2: quantum mechanics, 1952 January-April (Box 16, Folder 224)
      - Notes for Physics 362: nuclear physics, 1952 June-August (Box 16, Folder 225)
      - Thesis I, undated (Box 17, Folder 226)
      - Thesis II, undated (Box 17, Folder 227)
      - Thesis III, undated (Box 17, Folder 228)
      - Thesis IV, undated (Box 18, Folder 229)
      - Thesis V, undated (Box 18, Folder 230)
      - Thesis, undated (Box 18, Folder 231)
      - Thesis, undated (Box 19, Folder 232)
    - Taft School records, 1939-1943 (Box 19, Folder 233)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1980-1983, undated (Box 19, Folder 234-238)
  - Physics articles
    - "Observation of Hadronic Charm Production in a High Resolution Streamer Chamber Experiment", 1980 (Box 19, Folder 239-240)
  - Physics conferences
    - American Physical Society Annual Meeting (New York), 1963 (Box 20, Folder 241)
    - International Conference on Elementary Particles (Heidelberg), 1967 (Box 20, Folder 242)
    - International Conference on Elementary Particles (Heidelberg), 1967 (Box 20, Folder 243)
    - International Conference on Experimental Meson Spectroscopy (New York), 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 244)
    - International Conference on High Energy Physics (Dubna), 1964 (Box 20, Folder 245-248)
    - International Conference on High Energy Physics (Madison, WI), 1980 (Box 20, Folder 249-250)
    - International Conference on High Energy Physics (Madison, WI), 1980 (Box 21, Folder 251)
    - International Conference on Instrumentation for High Energy Physics at CERN (Geneva), 1962 (Box 21, Folder 252-253)
    - International Conference on Instrumentation for High Energy Physics at Stanford University (Stanford, CA), 1966 (Box 21, Folder 254)
    - Miscellaneous material, undated (Box 21, Folder 255)
    - Topical Conference on Resonant Particles at Ohio University (Athens, OH), 1967 (Box 21, Folder 256)
  - Precision Encoder and Pattern Recognition Device (PEPR)
    - Accounts, 1977-1983 (Box 21, Folder 257)
    - Collaboration, 1970-1971, undated (Box 21, Folder 258-259)
    - Correspondence
      - General, 1963-1968, undated (Box 21, Folder 260)
      - PDP-6, 1965-1968, undated (Box 21, Folder 261)
    - General, 1961-1963, undated (Box 21, Folder 262-263)
    - Hardware
      - Automatic tracking precision film reader for bubble chamber photographs: bids, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 264)
      - Automatic tracking precision film reader for bubble chamber photographs: bids, 1961, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 265)
      - Calibration grid, undated (Box 22, Folder 266)
      - Controller, undated (Box 22, Folder 267)
      - Controller: bids, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 268)
      - Diquads, undated (Box 22, Folder 269)
      - Equipment, 1964-1969, undated (Box 22, Folder 270)
      - Film drives, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 271)
      - Film drives, 1965-1969, undated (Box 22, Folder 272-274)
      - Magnetic tape units, 1965-1966, undated (Box 22, Folder 275-276)
      - Miscellaneous documents, 1960-1966, 1970, undated (Box 22, Folder 277-278)
      - PDP-1, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 279)
      - PDP-1 I/O BUS, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 280)
      - Reversed film development, 1968-1969, undated (Box 23, Folder 281)
    - Leptonic [Assgns?], 1966, undated (Box 23, Folder 282)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1962-1963, undated, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 283-285)
    - Proposal
      - "The Development and Construction of a Seven-Inch PEPR System at Yale University", 1963, undated (Box 23, Folder 286-287)
      - "The Development of High-Precision Cathode Ray Tube Techniques", 1963, undated (Box 23, Folder 288)
      - "A Digital Computer System for On-line Operation of PEPR", 1964-1965 (Box 23, Folder 289-290)
      - "A Digital Computer System for On-line Operation of PEPR", 1965 (Box 23, Folder 291)
      - "Incorporating a PDP-1 Computer into a Bubble Chamber Photograph Processing System", 1963, undated (Box 23, Folder 292)
    - University of Illinois, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 293)
  - Proposals
    - "To Study the Properties of Heavy Quark Production and Decay Using a High Resolution Streamer Chamber", 1980, 1981 January-Mar, 1981 May, 1981 August-1982, undated (Box 24, Folder 294)
      See also: box 5, folder 63-69 See also: box 8, folder 92 See also: box 8, folder 94
  - Ratti, Sergio, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 298)
  - Review of proposals, articles, books, etc., 1960-1982 (Box 24, Folder 299)
  - Sigma Xi, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 300)
  - Souder, Paul, [1982?] (Box 24, Folder 301)
  - Taft School
    - Correspondence, 1953-1959 (Box 24, Folder 302)
    - Correspondence, reports, and miscellaneous material, 1960-1962 (Box 24, Folder 303-306)
    - Correspondence, reports, and miscellaneous material, 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 307)
    - Board of Trustees meeting minutes, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 308)
    - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 309)
    - Reports and miscellaneous material, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 310-311)
    - Board of Trustees meeting minutes, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 312-313)
    - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 314)
    - Reports and miscellaneous material, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 315)
    - Board of Trustees meeting minutes, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 316)
    - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 317)
    - Reports and miscellaneous material, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 318)
    - Board of Trustees meeting minutes, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 319)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 320)
    - Reports and miscellaneous material, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 321)
    - Board of Trustees meeting minutes, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 322)
    - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 323)
    - Reports and miscellaneous material, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 324)
    - Board of Trustees meeting minutes, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 325)
    - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 326)
    - Reports and miscellaneous material, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 327-328)
    - Search Committee to replace John Esty as Headmaster of the Taft School, 1971-1972, undated (Box 27, Folder 329)
    - Board of Trustees meeting minutes, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 330)
    - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 331)
    - Reports and miscellaneous material, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 332)
    - 30th Reunion, May 1973, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 333)
    - Board of Trustees meeting minutes, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 334)
    - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 335)
    - Reports and miscellaneous material, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 336)
    - Board of Trustees meeting minutes, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 337)
    - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 338)